One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Amigasa Village
قرية أميغاسا
So...
لِمَ كانا يلحقان بكِ إذًا؟
Well...
...بشأن ذلك
I went into town to do some shopping...
،ارتحلتُ إلى البلدة للتبضع
But on my way home, I ran into some of the evil one's men and their baboon.
وأثناء عودتي، صادفني ذانك الشريران مع البابون
To protect me, Komachiyo attacked the baboon...
وهاجم كوماتشيو البابون من أجل حمايتي
Ah, so that's why you guys were fighting.
فهمت، لهذا كانا يتقاتلان
Meanwhile...
...ولكن حينها
They stole what I had just bought!
سلبا مني كافة مقتنياتي
Out of frustration, I ended up saying something taboo.
ومن شدّة استيائي، تفوهت بما يخالف القانون
When the Kozuki Clan comes back, they'll teach you a lesson!
حينما تعود عشيرة الكوزكي، سيُلقنونكم درسًا لن تنسوه
What was that?!
ماذا قلتِ؟
Let me go!
!أفلِتني
I thought I'd never see my home again,
ظننت أنني لن أعود إلى المنزل أبدًا
but thanks to you, I got away!
لكنني نجوت بفضلك يا أخي الكبير لوفي
So please let me return the favor!
لذلك دعني أردّ لك المعروف
Oh! Sounds great!
أجل، سيساعدني ذلك
I just got here, so I have a lot of questions.
بلغتُ بلاد وانو توًّا، فلديّ كمٌّ هائلٌ من الأسئلة
Okay then!
!مفهوم، تحتاج إلى طعام
Is this okay?
أهذا المكان مناسب؟
It is!
!أجل
No enemies can find it here.
لن تطلها يد عدوٍ هنا
Damn!
سحقًا... لا شيء صالح للأكل كما توقعت
Big Bro!
!يا أخي الكبير
Let's go now!
!لنذهب حالًا
I'd like to invite you over for a treat!
!أودّ استضافتك على وجبة
Big Bro! Hihimaru! This way!
من هذا الاتجاه يا أخي وهيهيمارو
Komachiyo A Lion-Dog
كوماتشيو كوماينو
Hihimaru A New Friend
هيهيمارو رفيق جديد
His name is Hihimaru?
اسمه هيهيمارو إذًا؟
I just came up with it!
!سمّيته توًّا
I see.
.فهمت
I'm counting on you, Hihimaru!
!أعتمد عليك يا هيهيمارو
So there are types of pirates that I like and kinds I don't like!
!ثمة قراصنة أحبهم وآخرون أمقتهم حقًّا
You can like who you want.
.أنتِ حُرة بمحبة من تشائين
You're the strong and kind type.
!إنك قوي وطيب يا أخي الكبير
My house is over there.
يقبع منزلي هناك
There's a village in the mountains?
هل توجد قرية بين الجبال؟
No, not anymore!
كلا، لم يعد لها وجود الآن
It's just my master and me now.
لا يعيش فيها حاليًّا سوايَ ومعلمي
I'm training to one day become...
...أنا أتدرب لأصبح في المستقبل
a bewitching kunoichi!
!كونويتشي فاتنة
"Bewitching"?
فاتنة؟
It's dirty, small, and stinky here.
إن المكان ضيّق ورثّ ورائحته كريهة
Big Bro, that's a little rude of you.
هذه وقاحة منك يا أخي الكبير
Oh, that smells delicious!
يا لها من رائحة زكية
It's almost done!
!سينضج قريبًا
Is it ready yet, Tama?!
ألم يجهز الطعام بعد يا تاما؟
It's ready!
!لقد نضج
Here you go.
!تفضل
Go ahead and dig in, Big Bro!
،بالهناء والعافية
Freshly-cooked rice!
!أرز مدخّن طازج
Thank you for the meal!
!شكرًا على الوجبة
It's delicious!
!لذيذ
Aren't you gonna have any?
ألن تأكلي؟
No, not now.
كلا، لن آكل الآن
I can't become a ninja if I'm not light on my feet!
لن أصبح كونويتشي إن لم أكن رشيقة
Seconds, please!
!المزيد
So quick!
!سريع
But that was all I cooked.
لكنني لم أطبخ المزيد
We're out of pickles too...
وأيضًا كان ذلك آخر ما تبقى من البهارات
A-All right then.
...هـ-هكذا إذًا
I was just joking when I asked for seconds.
كنتُ أمازحكِ
I gotta go to the bathroom.
سأذهب إلى الحمام
It wasn't enough, but it was kind of her to cook for me.
رغم أنني لم أشبع، إلا أنها غمرتني بكرمها
She's a good kid, that Tama...
إن تاما لفتاةً طيبة
Who the hell are you?!
!من تكون أيها اللعين؟
No, it's not!
لا، ليس هو
Why are you freeloading around here?!
لماذا أنت مستلقٍ هنا؟
Don't tell me you ate the rice.
أيعقل أنك أكلت الأرز؟
I did.
.نعم
Who are–
-ومن تكـ
You fool!
!أيها المعتوه
Keep quiet, stomach!
!كفّي عن القرقرة يا معدتي
It's disgraceful!
!هذا ليس من شيمنا
Wait!
!تمهّل
Wh-Who are you?!
من أنت؟
I'm only here because Tama cooked for me.
أتيتُ إلى هنا لأن تاما دعتني لتناول الطعام
Why would Otama cook for you?
لماذا عساها تدعوك لتناول الطعام؟
How many days do you think it's been since she last ate anything?!
أتعرف كم يومًا مضى على آخر وجبة تناولتها تلك الطفلة؟
Despite how hard she works everyday to weave and sell hats,
رغم أنها تنسج القبعات كل يوم وتبيعها في السوق
there is barely enough money to sustain even a single person!
إلا أننا بالكاد نكسب قوت شخص واحد
Sometimes we eat barnyard grass, and that's if we're lucky.
نضطر أحيانًا إلى تناول الأعشاب والحشائش
But at least, twice a year,
لكنني أحرص على أن تتناول الأرز في يوم ميلادها ورأس السنة على الأقل
So I sent her to town with some money
لهذا أعطيتها مالًا اليوم وأرسلتها إلى البلدة لتشتري الأرز بمناسبة يوم ميلادها الثامن
What lowlife would eat her rice?!
فلماذا أكلته أيها اللعين؟
Master!
!يا معلمي
Please stop!
!توقف رجاءً
Forgive me for cooking it without asking!
سامحني على طبخ الأرز له دون إذنك
But...
...ولكن
he saved my life!
هذا الرجل أنقذ حياتي
Don't bring dishonor upon me!
فأرجوك لا توصمني بالعار
I'll weave even more hats!
سأنسج عديدًا من القبعات مجددًا
So please forgive me!
!لذا سامحني رجاءً
Just let me return the favor to Big Bro Luffy properly...
...دعني أردّ المعروف لأخي الكبير لوفي
Please...
...أرجوك
Otama!
!أوتاما
Tama!
!تاما
Hey, Tama!
!يا تاما
She's done something foolish!
يا لفعلتها الحمقاء
She drank the river water to ease her hunger.
أظنها شربت من مياه النهر لتخفي جوعها
Water?
مياه؟
The river water in this country...
...مياه أنهار هذه البلاد
is polluted by liquid waste from Kaido's factories!
!ملوثة بمخلفات مصانع كايدو
For a small girl like her, it's like drinking poison.
ما زالت طفلة، لذا تلك المياه الملوثة بمثابة السُم لجسدها
Then, why are you living here?!
!لماذا تعيشان هنا إذًا؟
There are places that would be a bit better.
،بوسعنا العيش في أماكن أفضل
But she's waiting here.
...لكنها تنتظر هنا
For someone who promised to return...
رجلًا قد وعدها أنه سيعود...
A pirate named Ace!
!قرصانٌ يُدعى إيس
Tama...
...تاما
The Ace that you're waiting for...
...هل إيس الذي تنتظرينه
is Portgas D. Ace, right?
هو بورتغاس دي إيس؟
Do you know him?
...أتعرفه
Big Bro...
يا أخي الكبير؟
Yeah.
.أجل
Ace is dead.
.إيس مات
That's a lie...
...هذه كذبة
That's a lie!
!هذه كذبة
Big Bro, you're a liar!
!أنت كاذب يا أخي الكبير
Tama!
!تاما
Otama!
!أوتاما
Pull yourself together, Tama!
!تماسكي يا تاما
She fainted.
فقدت وعيها
So Ace visited Wano too...
إذًا فقد زارَ إيس بلاد وانو أيضًا؟
Are you a demon or something?!
هل أنت شيطان أيها اللعين؟
How could you tell Otama so casually that Ace died?
كيف تخبرها بموت إيس بهذه البساطة؟
But it's true.
.لكنها الحقيقة
Even if it's true, that wasn't the right time!
حتى لو كانت الحقيقة، فلم يكن الوقت مناسبًا لإخبارها
But no matter how long she waits, Ace won't come back!
لكن إيس لن يعود مهما طال انتظارها
But still...
...حتى مع ذلك
you should've considered when and how to say it!
كان عليك مراعاة مشاعرها وإخبارها في الوقت المناسب
You clearly lack a sense of tact!
!يا لك من عديم إحساس
Who the hell are you anyway?!
من تكون أصلًا؟
I'm Luffy, the man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
أنا لوفي، الرجل الذي سيصير ملك القراصنة
What?! You're a pirate?!
ماذا؟ قرصان؟
I generally don't like pirates!
لا أطيق القراصنة عمومًا
Old guy, who are you?!
ومن أنت أيها العجوز؟
I am Hitetsu.
.أنا هيتيتسو
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
I'm a swordsmith.
.صانعُ سيوفٍ
Tenguyama Hitetsu Swordsmith (And a Collector of Beautiful Kokeshi Dolls)
تينغوياما هيتيتسو صانع سيوف (وجامع دمى الكوكيشي الجميلة)
Ace is now gone!
لن يرجع إيس أبدًا
Take Tama and move to a better place!
خذ تاما وانتقلا إلى مكانٍ أفضل
I truly want to do so.
بصراحة، أريد هذا بشدة
But, for some time now...
...ولكن حتى أنا
I've been waiting for someone here myself.
أنتظر شخصًا منذ زمن طويل
There are only the two of us here now, but this was once Amigasa Village.
لم نكن وحيديْن هنا
Around a year ago...
لكن قبل حوالي سنة
a new headliner joined Kaido's army and came here.
قصدها رجل أصبح أحد شينوتشي كايدو حديثًا
He was a pirate named X Drake.
!قرصانًا يُدعى ديس دريك
He defeated the five samurai vital to the village...
هزم الساموراي الخمسة الذين كانوا يحمون القرية
and everything was destroyed.
ودمّر القرية بأكملها
Now, the only prosperous place in Wano...
...المكان المزدهر الوحيد في بلاد وانو حاليًّا
is the Flower Capital where Shogun Orochi lives.
هي عاصمة الزهور حيث يعيش الشوغن أوروتشي
Everywhere else...
أما كل مكانٍ آخر في البلاد فقد حوّله كايدو وأتباعه إلى مناطق برية تسودها الفوضى
It was four years ago when that man came here.
جاء ذلك الرجل إلى هنا قبل أربع سنوات
This village was always poor...
طالما كانت هذه القرية ترزح تحت وطأة الفقر والمجاعة
and without enough to live on, people often died of hunger.
وسكانها يعانون من عوزٍ شديد، فيموتون من شدة الجوع غالبًا
Just when we thought that the village was doomed...
...وحينما ظننا أننا هالكون لا محالة
Ace washed up on the beach.
انجرف إيس إلى الشاطئ
The villagers stole all the food and water...
هرع أهل القرية إلى أولئك القراصنة المنكوبين
from those helpless pirates.
وسرقوا كل ما عندهم من طعامٍ وشراب
They ate it all to survive.
ونجوا بعدما تناولوا كل ما سرقوه
Ace watched them finish everything,
كان إيس يشاهدهم أثناء التهامهم لمؤونتهم
then, to everyone's surprise, he easily untied himself.
حلّ وثاقه فجأةً بكل سهولة
Everyone prepared for the retribution they thought was coming.
ظنوا جميعًا أنه سينتقم منهم
Did you have enough?
هل شبعتِ؟
Uh... Uh-huh.
.أ... أجل
Then it's time for something sweet!
حان وقت التحلية إذًا
Where can I find something for dessert?
أين أجد حلوى؟
Alright, I'll bring it right back here!
!حسنٌ، سأذهب لآتي بها
Everyone was stunned.
تفاجأ الجميع من ردّة فعله
Ace stayed at the village for several weeks.
مكث إيس في القرية عدة أسابيع
Otama was especially attached to him.
وكانت أوتاما تحديدًا متعلّقة به بشدة
I still can't believe shipwrecked pirates saved our lives.
...لا أصدق أن قراصنة تائهين قد أنقذوا حياتنا
I see.
!هكذا إذًا
Hey!
!أنت
Where can I get water and food?
أين أجد ماءً وطعامًا؟
And is there a doctor around here?
وهل من طبيب قريب من هنا؟
Don't tell me...
...أيعقل
I'm gonna take Tama...
...سآخذ تاما إليه
in return for giving me food!
تقديرًا للطعام الذي قدمته لي
Wait, you fool!
تمهّل أيها الأحمق
Your outlandish outfit is too conspicuous! Put this on!
!ملابسك تثير الريبة، ارتدِ هذه
Oh, it's a kimono!
!إنه كيمونو الكيمونو هو اللباس التقليدي في اليابان
Stay still!
!اثبت مكانك
Samurai armor would be cool, too!
أودّ ارتداء درع وخوذة أيضًا
No one wears that every day!
لا أحد يرتدي هذه في الحياة اليومية
You're good to go!
.هذا مناسب
There's a reason I can't go into town...
،هنالك سبب يمنعني من زيارة البلدة
so please take care of Otama!
!اعتنِ بأوتاما
I'll reimburse the doctor's fee later!
سأتدبر أجر الطبيب لاحقًا
If I can meet my friends before that, we'll get food and medical care for free!
إن قابلتُ رفاقي قبل ذلك، فسنحظى بالطعام والعلاج مجانًا
They'll help us!
سيساعدوننا
Look what you got there!
يبدو رائعًا
If I borrow this sword, I'll look like a real samurai!
سأستعير هذا السيف أيضًا لأبدو تمامًا كالساموراي
Okay, see you!
!حسنٌ، سأذهب
Tama! I'm taking you to a doctor now!
تاما، سآخذك إلى الطبيب حالًا
No, wait!
كلا، انتظر
You fool! You can't take that!
لا يمكنك أخذه أيها الأحمق
It's blasphemy to play around with a famous sword!
إنه سيف شهيرٌ لا يحمله أي أحد
My ancestor, Kotetsu, forged that world-famous sword!
!صنعه أحد أسلافي «كوتيتسو»، إنه سيف ذائع الصيت في العالم
It's one of only twenty-one great grade swords!
فهو أحد السيوف الـ21 من الفئة الممتازة
It's called Kitetsu II!
!واسمه كيتيتسو الثاني
Listen!
!أنصت
Of the numerous swords in the world,
من بين سيوف العالم التي لا تُحصى، توجد سيوف ممتازة صنعها أعظم الحدادين
And the finest among them are called...
:وتُصنّف حسب جودتها
the fifty fine grade swords,
السيوف الـ50 من الفئة الجيدة
the twenty-one great grade swords,
الـ21 من الفئة الممتازة
and the twelve supreme grade swords.
والـ12 من الفئة العظيمة
There's a story behind Kitetsu in particular...
وسيف كيتيتسو يتميّز بقصّةٍ تحديدًا
He's gone!
!رحل
See you! I'm gonna take the sword!
إلى اللقاء، سأستعير السيف
Hey! Listen to me!
أنت، أصغ إليّ
Wait! Wait!
!مهلًا انتظر
I said no!
لا يمكنك أخذه
Then, let me borrow your sword instead!
بادلني بسيفك إذًا
This is also a named blade!
!هذا نصلٌ شهير أيضًا
The one you took is cursed!
!السيف الذي أخذته ملعون
It's quite scary.
!إنه مخيف للغاية
I do not wish to carry it!
لا أريد حمله، لأنه يصيب المرء بلعنة
I'm leaving now, Grandpa Nose!
أنا ذاهب يا عجوز الأنف الطويل
I won't forgive you if anything happens to Otama!
!لن أسامحك إن أصاب أوتاما مكروه
Yeah, I'll save her at any cost!
أجل، سأنقذها حتمًا
And don't forget to return the sword!
!ولا تنسَ إعادة السيف
Answer me!
!أجبني
Why aren't you responding?!
لِمَ لا تجيبني؟
Oh, it's the dog!
أيها الكلب، هل ستحملنا؟
This is much easier!
!هذا مريح
Take us straight to town!
أسرِع بنا إلى البلدة
Oh, Tama! You're up!
استيقظتِ يا تاما؟
Big Bro, where are we going on Komachiyo?
يا أخي الكبير، إلى أين يأخذنا كوماتشيو؟
To the doctor.
.إلى الطبيب
Does this dog know the way?
هل الكلب يعرف الطريق؟
Ace is dead.
.إيس مات
Whoa-whoa, stop! You're gonna fall!
توقفي، ستسقطين
Big Bro, you're a liar!
أنت كاذب يا أخي الكبير
Ace can't come back!
إيس لن يعود
Everyone knows what happened during the Summit War.
الجميع يعرف أحداث حرب القمة
But...
...لكنه
he promised me...
!وعدني
Ace will come back!
!إيس سيعود
Ace!
!إيس، خذني معك إلى البحر
I'm old enough!
!أنا ناضجة بما يكفي
But you're only five.
لكنكِ ما زلتِ في الخامسة من عمرك
I'm already five!
!لقد تجاوزتُ الخامسة
Oh, you know what you're doing there.
أنت بارع في هذا
Sure do.
...أجل
You're gonna leave here soon, right?
ستغادر المكان قريبًا، صحيح؟
Yeah! I have to finish this before then...
أجل، لكن عليّ إنهاء هذه قبل مغادرتي
I...
لا أودّ توديعك أنت والبقية
Tama...
...تاما
We'll come back!
!سنأتي مجددًا بعد أن نصبح طاقم قراصنة أكبر بكثير
Then, will you let me join your crew?
إذًا ستضمني إلى طاقمك حينها؟
I wanna go on adventures with you!
أودّ خوض مغامرة معك
To be a pirate, you must be strong!
يجب أن تصبحي قوية لتصبحي قرصانةً
When I come back...
...حين أعود
if you've become something like a bewitching kunoichi, I'll take you along.
إن أصبحتِ كونويتشي فاتنة، فسأصطحبكِ معي
Ace! Does she really need to be "bewitching"?!
يا إيس، هل فاتنة ضرورية؟
Ace!
!إيس
I got it!
!فهمت، هذا وعد بيننا
We were very close...
رابطتي قوية به
He said he'd come back...
قال إنه سيعود مجددًا
Big Bro, you don't know how nice he is!
أنت لا تعرف مدى طيبة إيس يا أخي الكبير
That's why you don't understand my pain!
!لهذا لا تدرك ألمي
It doesn't hurt, but stop hitting me...
توقفي عن ضربي... حتى وإن كان لا يؤثر بي
How could talk so casually about him dying?!
كيف تقول أنه مات بتلك البساطة؟
You're a dummy, Big Bro!
!أنت غبيٌّ حقًّا يا أخي الكبير
Grandpa Nose was right...
!كان عجوز الأنف الطويل محقًّا
It really is a wilderness!
!إنها أرض قاحلة حقًّا
It's a tiger!
!نمر
And a boar!
!وخنزير
What is that?!
وما ذلك؟
Th-That's a Sharkodile!
!إ-إنه وانيزامي
Talk about wild!
!البريّة مذهلة
Just eat them if you're ever hungry!
يمكنكم تناولها إن جعتم
We can't...
...لا يمكننا
All the samurai who used to hunt them have either been arrested or become bandits...
كل الساموراي الأقوياء والقادرين على اصطيادها
Besides...
...وعلاوةً على ذلك
Animals drink the polluted river water, too...
تشرب الحيوانات من مياه النهر الملوثة أيضًا
so people get poisoned if they eat them.
فإنَّ أكل هذه الحيوانات بمثابة السمّ بالنسبة لنا
But they look so delicious!
...مع أنها تبدو شهية
How could they?!
!هذا لا يُغتفر
Is that smoke from the factory?
هل مصدر الدخان ذاك هو المصنع؟
Yes!
...أجل
They have a mine and a weapons factory...
لديهم هناك منجم ومصنع أسلحة
so a lot of Kaido's subordinates are there.
لذا هو محاط بعديدٍ من أتباع كايدو
What do they eat?
ماذا يأكلون؟
The shogun and Kaido have... an untainted farm...
...الشوغن وكايدو يمتلكان مزرعة غير ملوثة
just for themselves.
...لأنفسهم فقط
That's why they have clean water and rice...
...لهذا تتوفر لديهم مياه نقية وأرز
and fish...
...وأسماك
and lots... of meat...
...ولحم... وفير
Man! So it's not like there isn't any on this island!
ثمة منطقة غنية بالخيرات إذًا؟
Hey! Tama! Are you all right?!
تاما، هل أنتِ بخير؟
Ouch!
!ساخنة
I think you're getting warmer!
!ارتفعت درجة حرارتك
Hang on!
!تماسكي
I'll get you to a doctor soon!
سآخذك إلى طبيبٍ حالًا
If the enemy has food and water, that's good enough for me!
سيفيدني إن صادفتُ عدوًّا يحمل طعامًا وشرابًا
Hurry up, boy!
أسرِع أيها الكلب
Please forgive me!
!رجاءً سامحاني
Wait, woman!
!انتظري أيتها المرأة
Drop everything you have!
ضعي كل ما لديكِ
Help! Somebody!
ليساعدني أحد
Damn! I'll make you pay for this!
!سحقًا، ستدفع الثمن
Step back, lady...
يا امرأة، تراجعي
You're that fugitive, Zorojuro!
!أنت ذلك المجرم الهارب زوروجورو
You fools.
...أيها اللعين
You have sake...
...ذلك الساكي
Hand it over!
!سلّمني إياه
Sir Samurai!
!ساموراي-ساما
I don't know who you are, but thank you for saving my life!
لا أعرف من تكون، لكن شكرًا جزيلًا لك لإنقاذ حياتي
Oh, don't mention it.
لا داعي للشكر
I wanted their sake anyway... uh...
...أردتُ الساكي فحسب
verily.
.يقينًا...
But I want to return the favor.
!لكنني أودّ ردّ جميلك
Then, more sake!
!قدّمي لي ساكي إذًا
Oh, I don't have any.
.لا أملك منه
That's Zoro!
!إنه زورو
Hey, Zoro!
!يا زورو، هذا أنا
Luffy!
!لوفي
You made it!
!أتيت إذًا
It's good to finally see you!
!قابلتك أخيرًا
Zoro!
!زورو
Long time no see...
...طال
Long time no see, verily and stuff!
!طال الفراق يقينًا
Is everyone with you?
هل الجميع معك؟
Yeah, but we got separated...
أجل، لكنني افترقتُ عنهم
I'm sure they're okay though!
حسنٌ... أظنهم بخير
You have meat!
!إنك تحمل لحمًا؟! أعطني بعضه
There are a bunch of fish and animals to hunt here, Luffy!
يمكنك اصطياد عديدًا من الأسماك والحيوانات في هذه المنطقة يا لوفي
You'll never be short of food!
لن ينقصك الطعام أبدًا
No, be careful!
كلا، توخّ الحذر
The water around here is poisonous!
مياه هذه المنطقة ملوثة
So I heard the meat and fish are poisonous, too!
سمعتُ أنّ اللحوم والأسماك مسممة أيضًا
I see. That's why I have a stomachache.
فهمت، هذا يفسر سبب ألم معدتي
Anyway, Zoro, come with us!
على أي حال يا زورو، تعال معنا
A lot has happened, and I'm on my way to take her to a doctor.
حدثت عديد من الأمور، وأودّ أخذها إلى طبيب
A sick kid!
!طفلة مريضة
You shouldn't be stopping to eat!
هل هذا وقت الأكل؟
Don't worry!
لا تقلق، سآكل بسرعة
Just eat already!
!كلها بسرعة
Okay!
!حسنًا
Are you...
...هل أنت
the ronin who is wanted across the country, Zorojuro,
...الرونين المطلوب في كل أنحاء البلاد زوروجورو
and members of his clan?
ورفيقه؟...
Oh?! He's...
...إنه
That's right...
.أجل
Seems like he works for Kaido now.
يبدو أنه أصبح تابعًا لكايدو
Straw Hat!
!قبعة القش
I was on my way to Kuri Beach...
كنتُ متوجهًا إلى شاطئ كوري
but you caused the ruckus there, didn't you?
لكن يبدو أنك من افتعل المشكلات هناك، أليس كذلك؟
Two of my subordinates and one baboon went missing...
فقدتُ تابِعَيْن لي وبابون
Basil Hawkins One of the Beast Pirates' Headliners
باسيل هوكينز شينوتشي في قراصنة الوحوش
The possibility that you guys have something to do with it...
...احتمال أنكما متورطان في ذلك
is 98 percent.
...في المئة
But...
...ولكن
that doesn't matter.
!ذلك لا يهم
In Wano, you either follow the strong or become their prey...
في هذه البلاد، إما تتبع القوي أو تصبح فريسته
Luffy, Kin'emon told us...
...لوفي، أخبرنا كينيمون
not to cause a disturbance.
.بألّا نثير جلبة
Well, then I'll just have to...
...حسنٌ، إذًا
apologize to him later!
علينا أن نعتذر لاحقًا